fancyladies.com 2012-11-07

# Privacy Policy - Fancyladies.com

**Privacy Policy**

Fancyladies respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy informs you the way your information is collected online and how that information is used. This privacy policy ("Policy") applies to the websites of Fancyladies.com. This statement is readily available on our home page and at the bottom of every Fancyladies Web page.

**Personal Information We Collected**

We collect information about you in various ways when you use our site. For example, we collect your name, email address, postal address, phone number, fax number and other information you provide us on our site. We also collect credit card numbers and other forms of payment information if you purchase products through our site. We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect on our site.

When you visit our site, some information about your visit is automatically collected by Fancyladies systems. For example, when you visit our site your computer's or mobile device operating system, application software, Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and language, peripherals, and the websites you visited before our site are logged automatically. We also collect information about your usage and activity on our site including information about your orders, purchases, and cart activity.

**Cookies**. We automatically collect information using "cookies." Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our site and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our site.

**Web Beacons**. We also collect information using Web beacons. Web beacons are electronic images used on our site and in our emails. We use Web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

**How We Use the Collected Information**

The information we collects to understand your needs and interests helps Fancyladies to provide more and better products and service to you. For example, Fancyladies may use your information to:

  * provide and deliver products and services you request
  * send you transaction related information, including confirmations, order processing, shipment, product and services information updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages communicate with you about products and services
  * respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
  * update you on new promotions and rewards, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by Fancyladies;
  * ask you to participate in contests and surveys to measure our performance and improve our products, services and customer experience

**Your Controls and Choice**

Fancyladies gives you the choice of receiving a variety of information that complements our products and services. You can subscribe to receive our subscriptions, newsletters and promotions. And if you do not want to be informed our promotional email, you can easily unsubscribe from us by contact us at [newsletter@fancyladies.com](mailto:newsletter@fancyladies.com?subject=unsubscibe%20newsletters%20from%20fancyladies.com).

**Security of Your Personal Information**  
Fancyladies takes reasonable steps to help protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.
